(呼出)
(exhales)
好的，宝贝，第一个候选人马上就到。
Okay, babe, first candidate   should be here any minute.
咖啡好了吗?
Is the coffee ready?
茶壶已经充好电了。
The tea kettle is charged.
英式早餐，花草茶，
English breakfast, herbal tea,
绿茶，无咖啡因的，还有普通的。
green tea, decaf,   and (clicks tongue) regular.
你确定这些椒盐卷饼棒是素食的吗?
Hey, are we sure these pretzel sticks are vegan?
我想是的。候选人中有素食主义者吗?
I think so. Is one of the candidates vegan?
既然是女祭司，我只能假设。
Well, with the priestess,    I have to assume.
我不想冒犯她，你知道的。
I don't wanna      offend her, you know.
我担心你给我的压力太大了。
I'm worried you're putting    too much pressure on this.
嗯…
Uh...
不，我不是。
No, I am not.
这位司仪会让我们在上帝面前团结起来
This officiant is gonna     unite us in front of God
我们的余生。
for the rest of our lives.
我是说，这是件大事。
I mean, it is a big deal.
好吧。对，但对的人会找到我们的。
Okay.    Yeah, but the right person    will find us.
你只要做你自己，别担心。
You just have to be yourself   and not worry.
如果她不想要椒盐卷饼棒，
And if she doesn't      want a pretzel stick,
她不会吃的。
she won't eat it.
因为你认为他们不是素食主义者。
Because you think        they're not vegan.
我就知道。这是个愚蠢的想法。
I knew it.       It's a stupid idea.
我要把这些扔了。
I'm gonna throw these out.
嘿。
Hey.
-看着我。——(TK叹了口气)
-Look at me.            -(TK sighs)
这应该很有趣，好吗?
This is supposed        to be fun, alright?
一切都会好起来的。
Everything will be okay.
好吧。
Okay.
让我们找点乐子吧。
Let's have some fun.
Mazel tov关于订婚。
Mazel tov        on the engagement.
芬克尔拉比，谢谢你能来。
Rabbi Finkel,      thank you for coming.
当然可以。
Of course.
我们该叫你萨瓦德牧师吗
So should we call you      Pastor Savard
还是妮可牧师?
or Pastor Nicole?
妮可很好。
Oh, Nicole's fine.
紫水晶，或者女神。
Amethyst, or goddess,      if you prefer.
很高兴见到你，紫水晶。
It's very nice      to meet you, Amethyst.
卡洛斯·雷耶斯:我们可以叫你汤姆吗?
CARLOS REYES:       Can we call you Tom?
汤姆牧师，如果你不介意的话。
Uh, Reverend Tom,        if you don't mind.
我上神学院七年不是为了做汤姆。
I didn't go to divinity school for seven years to be just Tom.
容我说一句，你们俩都有光芒四射的光环。
If I may say, you two     both have radiant auras.
-哦，谢谢。amethyst:紫水晶
-Why, thank you.   -AMETHYST: I've always been
拥有第二视觉。
blessed with second sight.
那些是椒盐卷饼棒吗?
Are those pretzel sticks?
是的。
Yeah.
(处理)
(crunching)
你确定你愿意为，
Are-are you sure you're okay with officiating a wedding for,
你知道，像我们这样的人?
you know, folks like us?
谁说他是个年轻的犹太男孩
Who's to say     a nice young Jewish boy
找不到一个英俊的天主教徒?
couldn't find love with      a handsome Catholic?
我们是a面教会。
We're a Side A church.
这意味着我们相信所有爱的关系
That means that we believe     all loving relationships
在上帝的眼中是平等的。
are equal in the eyes of God.
真漂亮。
That's really beautiful.
我给你带来了几段经文
I brought you     a few scripture passages
我觉得你们应该读一下
on the subject that I think would be great for you to read.
卡洛斯:嗯。
CARLOS: Hmm.
你的是一种淡蓝色的鼠尾草。
Yours is a cool blue       of a sage.
你的是火红的，充满激情的红色。
Yours is a fiery,         passionate red.
当你们聚在一起，
And when you come together,
你们的夫妻光环变成了棱镜…
your couple aura    turns into a prismatic...
紫色?
Purple?
你也有视力吗?
Do you have the sight, too?
不，我只是熟悉色轮。
No, I'm just familiar      with the color wheel.
我对同性婚姻的建议是
The passage I recommend     for same-sex unions is
“Ani L'Dodi V'Dodi Li。”
"Ani L'Dodi V'Dodi Li."
我是我心爱的——
I am my beloved's--
-我的爱人是我的。是的。
-And my beloved is mine.     -RABBI FINKEL: Yes.
我猜是希伯来学校遗留下来的东西。
I guess something stuck     from Hebrew school.
(笑)
(chuckles)
人们并不总是喜欢听到这些。
And people don't always     like to hear it.
但有时光有爱是不够的。
But sometimes love isn't enough.
婚姻是你所做过的最大的承诺。
Marriage is the greatest   commitment you'll ever make.
尤其是对你们这些男孩。
Especially for you boys.
你们将永远在一起。
You'll be joined together    for eternity.
在地狱里燃烧。
Burning in hell.
-哇。嗯。
-Wow.              -Hmm.
谢谢你的提醒，Tom。是的。
-TK STRAND: Thanks for      the heads up, Tom.      -Yep.
-我能提个建议吗?-是的。
-If I may offer        a piece of advice?        -Yeah.
不要听噪音。
Don't listen to the noise.
相信我，会有很多噪音的。
And believe me,  there will be a lot of noise.
嗬，嗬，嗬。哈哈哈。
Ho, ho, ho. Ha, ha, ha.
他，他，他。我，我，我。
He, he, he. Me, me, me.
迪。迪。他，他，他。
Dee, dee.           He, he, he.
我，我，我。你，你，你。
Me, me, me.        Thee, thee, thee.
26号你有空吗?
You available on the 26th?
我不相信基督教日历。或时间。
I don't believe in     the Christian calendar.     Or time.
所以现在剩下要做的就是招收你们
So all that's left to do now   is to enroll you
在一些课程中。
in some classes.
有些课吗?当然是皈依。
-Some classes?     -To convert, of course.
妮可牧师:我不喜欢强迫任何人做任何事，
PASTOR NICOLE:  I don't like to force anything  on anyone,
但我总是要求我的夫妻们
but I always ask        my couples to have
现在是大而艰难的对话
the big, difficult         conversations now
在你结婚之前。
before you get married.
关于工作，财务，爱情。
About work, finances, romance.
相信我，我们有过很多艰难的对话。
Oh, trust me, we've had all of the difficult conversations.
那孩子呢?
And what about kids?
我们不会有孩子的。等不及要吃了。
-CARLOS:  We're not gonna have kids.  -TK: Can't wait to have them.
怎么啦？
What?
(主题音乐播放)
(theme music plays)
那么谁是你的主要竞争者?
CARLOS: So who's your leading contender?
说实话，紫水晶有我的票
I'll be honest,       Amethyst had my vote
直到她说我有蓝色光环
right up until the moment   she said I had a blue aura.
大家都知道它是翠绿色的。
Everybody knows       it's emerald green.
我们真的不谈这个吗，卡洛斯?
Are we seriously not gonna     talk about this, Carlos?
谈什么?
CARLOS:         Talk about what?
我们之间刚刚拉开的鸿沟?
The gaping chasm that just opened up between us?
没有巨大的鸿沟。
There's no gaping chasm.
卡洛斯，你什么时候不想要孩子了?
Carlos, since when do you    not wanna have kids?
我什么时候说过了?
Since when did I ever say I did?
我不知道，我只是假设。
I don't know,    I-I guess I just assumed.
你还以为我没有妻子。
You also assumed      I didn't have a wife.
你真有趣。
You're so funny.
我们怎么从来没谈过这个?
How have we never had       this conversation?
我不知道。我没想过这个问题。
I don't know. It's not something I've been thinking about.
而且我们一直在忙工作
Plus, we've been busy working,
想找点乐子
trying to have a little fun
当我们没有昏迷或被绑架的时候。
when we're not in comas     or being abducted.
是啊，但是你…你喜欢孩子，卡洛斯。
Yeah, but you...      you love kids, Carlos.
我喜欢别人家的孩子。
I love other people's kids.
好吧。你的侄子和侄女呢
Okay. What about     your nephews and nieces
或者维加上尉的双胞胎或者小查理?
or-or Captain Vega's twins    or baby Charlie?
别人家的孩子。
All other people's kids.
是啊，但你和他们相处得很好。
Yeah, but you're        so great with them.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我对马也很在行。
I'm also great with horses.
还有一些你可能不知道的事情。
Something else    you probably didn't know.
TK，我只是想让我们有机会做回自己。
TK, I just want us    to have a chance to be us.
我还有很多事想和你一起做。
There are so many things    I still wanna do with you.
我想和你一起去爬长城。
I wanna hike     the Great Wall with you.
我想在托斯卡纳和你睡个懒觉。我想,
I wanna sleep in       in Tuscany with you.       I wanna--
宝贝，你都没来过这里，而且你讨厌睡懒觉。
Babe, you don't even hike here, and you hate sleeping in.
是的。我们还是没一起去过纽约。
Yeah. We've still never been   to New York together.
你知道他们允许你这么做的
Well, you know       that they allow you
带孩子来纽约吗
to bring children         into New York?
我只是觉得我们离准备好还差得远
I just don't think we're  anywhere close to being ready
对于那种程度的责任。
for that level        of responsibility.
我们甚至从来没有养过宠物。
We've never even had a pet.
卢。
Lou.
卢?tk:卢。
-Lou?            -TK: Lou.
我们的宠物蜥蜴。
Our pet lizard.
那只蜥蜴五分钟后就逃走了
The lizard that escaped     five minutes
在你把它带回家之后
after you brought it       to the house
我们把它放回大自然了吗?
and that we've released     back into the wild?
所以你觉得我会是个糟糕的父亲。
So you think I'm gonna     make a terrible father.
我从没这么说过。
I never said that.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
但我认为…
But what I do think...
你会成为一个出色的丈夫。
is that you are going to make  a fantastic husband.
V8引擎在摩德纳设计
V8 engine designed in Modena
米兰皮革内饰。
with a Milanese        leather interior.
座位是加热的。
The seats are heated.
为了回答你的问题，
And to answer your question,
是的，点心是免费的。
yes, the pastries        are complimentary.
(咯咯地笑)哦，这太豪华了，米奇。
(chuckles)  Oh, it's awfully fancy, Mitch.
我是说，我们需要这么高级的东西吗?
I mean, do we need        something so fancy?
在我们经历了那么多之后?
After what we've been through?
这是宇宙欠我们的。
The universe owes it to us.
天灾毁坏了我们的婚房，我们就无家可归了。
We were unhoused   when an act of God   destroyed our marital abode.
哦,不。火吗?
Oh, no. Fire?
实际上是消防队。
Fire department, actually.
我们失去了一切。
We lost everything.
幸运的是，我叔叔最近去世了。
Luckily, my uncle        passed recently.
把他的复式公寓留给了我们。
Left us his duplex.
嗯,那是……好。
Well, that's... good.
我们还存了一点钱。
And we have     a little money put away.
将近50万美元。
Almost half a million dollars.
悲剧发生后，我们启动了GoFundMe网站
We started a GoFundMe      after the tragedy
看看人们对有需要的人有多慷慨。
to see how generous people can be to those in need.
它恢复了我们对人性的信心。
It restored      our faith in humanity.
现在我们冲水。
(singsongy)          Now we flush.
(呵呵)
(all chuckling)
那么，你说呢?
So, what do you say?
我不知道。
I don't know.
(轻微的笑)
(slight chuckle)
-我们再来点这个。我明白了。
-Let's get, uh, more of these.  -I gotcha.
我是说，人们捐了那笔钱
I mean, people        donated that money
这样我们就能买得起新房子了，
so we could afford a new home,
但我们现在有了。
but we have that now.
我们不应该还回去吗?
Shouldn't we give it back?
莱拉，当人们为有价值的事业捐款时，
Lila, when people donate     to a worthy cause,
他们这样做是为了让自己感觉良好。
they do it so they feel good.
你想让他们远离这种感觉吗?
Do you wanna take that feeling  away from them?
嗯，没有，但是…
Well, no, but it just...
感觉好奢侈。
feels so extravagant.
看，这就是所谓的贫穷心态，
See, that's what you call    a poverty mindset,
你必须克服这一点。
and you have to get over that.
我知道当你照镜子时，
I know when you look       in the mirror,
你看到一个来自拖车公园的新手。
you see a plebe      from the trailer park.
但你知道我看到了什么吗?
But you know what I see?
怎么啦？
What?
一个女王。
A queen.
女王的屁股属于
A queen whose butt belongs
-加热米兰皮革。——(Lila尖叫)
-on heated Milanese leather.   -(Lila squeals)
(笑)
(both chuckle)
这听起来并不可怕。
That doesn't sound terrible.
米奇(咯咯地笑):是的。
MITCH (chuckling): Yeah.
你不必感到内疚
You don't have to feel guilty
得到你应得的，莱拉
about getting     what you deserve, Lila.
你怎么看?
So what do you say?
♪♪
哦……我们买了!
Oh... We'll take it!
-(Lila呜呜叫)-(引擎轰鸣)
-(Lila whooping)        -(engine roaring)
(提高持续)
(whooping continues)
我的心都快跳出来了!
My heart is pumping       outta my chest!
-那是V8引擎。-Whoo-hoo !
-That's the V8.         -Whoo-hoo!
哦,是的!哇!
Oh, yes! Whoo!
(提高持续)
(whooping continues)
哇!
Whoo!
哦。哦!嘿!
Oh. Ohh! Hey!
米奇,米奇。那家伙想和我们赛跑。
Mitch, Mitch.  That guy is trying to race us.
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
我不知道，亲爱的。
I-I don't know, hon.
哦，得了吧。看看他。来吧。来吧。
Oh, come on. Look at him.    Come on. Come on.
来吧!
Come on!
加快!加快!
Speed up! Speed up!
你让那个垃圾袋从我们身边过去了!
You're lettin' that        trash bag pass us!
哇!别想，走吧，宝贝!
Whoo! Don't think,        just go, baby!
(呼出)
(exhales)
(引擎咆哮)
(engine roaring)
(紫色的)
(Lila whooping)
(莱拉和米奇尖叫)
(Lila and Mitch screaming)
-哇!米奇:Woo-hoo-hoo !
-Whoo!       -MITCH: Woo-hoo-hoo!
(莱拉和米奇尖叫着)
(Lila and Mitch     whooping and screaming)
四百五十马力!
Four hundred and fifty      horsepower!
去死吧!哈哈!
Suck it, plebe! Ha-ha!
(汽车缩放)
(cars zooming)
女王万岁，婊子!
All hail the queen, bitch!
哇!
Whoo!
上帝，我爱你。
God, I love you.
我也爱你，国王。
I love you too, king.
(笑着说)
(both laughing)
(莱拉和米奇尖叫)
(Lila and Mitch scream)
莱拉:慢点，慢点!
LILA:      Slow down, slow down!
我尝试!
I'm trying!
(轮胎尖叫)
(tires screeching)
(莱拉喘着气，裤子)
(Lila gasps, pants)
(卡车哔哔声)
(truck beeping)
(尖叫)
(both screaming)
莱拉:不!
LILA: No!
(肥料隆隆)
(manure rumbling)
(鸣喇叭，鸣汽笛)
(horns blaring, sirens wailing)
欧文·斯特兰德:发生了什么事?
OWEN STRAND:          What happened?
他们俩差点撞坏了汽车
Well, them two   nearly crashed their hot rod
放进我的侧翻车里。
into my side dumper.
几乎崩溃?
Nearly crashed?
男:是的，他们突然停了下来，
MAN: Well, yeah, they stopped short,
但我在垃圾堆里
but I was     in the middle of a dump.
-等等，这些都是肥料?是的。
-Wait, all that's manure?    -Yep.
高质量的有机食品。
High-quality organic.
他们没受伤，但他们。
They ain't hurt none,      but they're, uh,
有点插进去了。
kinda planted in there.
你在开玩笑吗?帽。
Are you kidding me? Cap.
你看到那是谁了吗?
Do you see who that is?
等等，他们怎么这么眼熟?
Wait, why do they look familiar?
他们是离家出走的那对夫妇。
NANCY GILLIAN:     They're that couple     from that runaway house.
等等，那些对Marjan提起诉讼的人吗?
Wait, the ones who filed  the complaint against Marjan?
一样的。哦，是的。
-PAUL STRICKLAND: The same.    -MATEO CHAVEZ: Oh, yeah.
杰拉尔德先生和太太，我发誓……呼吸。
Mr. and Mrs. Geralds,    as I live and... breathe.
-你在开玩笑吧。——(Lila低声呻吟)
-Oh, you've gotta be kidding me. -(Lila whimpers)
-你受伤了吗?-不，我们没受伤。
-Are you hurt?       -No, we're not hurt.
-我们被困住了。——(Lila呻吟)
-We're just stuck.         -(Lila groaning)
卡住了，卡住了，动弹不得?
So stuck like,     stuck, stuck can't move?
如果我们能移动，你觉得我们还会坐在这里吗?
Well, do you think     we'd be sitting in here        if we could move?
我不太了解你，不能回答这个问题。
I don't know you well enough   to answer that question.
维加上尉，你要评估一下医疗伤害吗?
Captain Vega, you wanna   assess the medical injuries?
会做的事情。TK，测一下脉搏氧。
Will do. TK, get a pulse ox.
收到，上尉。
Copy that, Cap.
嘿，能给我架梯子吗?
Hey, can I get       a ladder over here?
(哽咽，咳嗽)哦，天哪。
(gags, coughs) Oh, God.
米奇，我吞了一些!
Mitch, I swallowed some!
那就闭上你的嘴，莱拉!
Well try keeping      your mouth shut, Lila!
(叹息)
(both groan)
-(莱拉咕哝着，叹了口气)-嘿，伙计们。
-(Lila grunts, sighs)      -Hey, guys.
莱拉:哦。(设备哔哔)
-LILA: Oh.        -(device beeping)
(叹息)
(both groan)
-很冷。- 96岁，美国。
-It's cold.       -Satting at 96, Cap.
一切都好了。
Everything's alright.
好吧。
Alright.
萃取稳定。
Stable for extraction.
斯特兰德船长，都归你了。
Captain Strand,        they're all yours.
是的。
Yeah.
(叹息)
(sighs)
嗯。
Huh.
嗯。唔唔。
Hmm. Mm-mmm.
-(莱拉呻吟)-什么?“嗯”什么?
-(Lila groaning)        -What? What "hmm"?
你为什么只是站在那里?
Why are you       just standing there?
我评估。
I'm assessing.
要评估什么?
What is there to assess?
带我们离开这里!
Get us out of here!
欧文:我们不急。
OWEN:       We don't wanna rush.
对吧，马尔瓦尼?
Isn't that right, Marwani?
对了，队长。
Oh, that's right, Cap.
可能会有错误。
There could be mistakes.
错误是不好的。
Mistakes are bad.
我的天啊。把我们拉出去。
Oh, my God.        Just pull us out.
欧文:我们可以把你拉出来。
OWEN:   We could just pull you out.
对吧，贾德?我们可以把他们拉出来。
Isn't that right, Judd?     We could pull 'em out.
我是说，我们可以把他们拉出来
Well, I mean,      we could pull 'em out,
但我们可能会直接把他们的胳膊扯下来。
but we'd probably just    pull their arms right off.
-什么?是的。
-What?        -JUDD RYDER: Yeah.
牛粪有重量
Cow manure weighs somewhere
在每立方码1200到1800磅之间，
between 1,200 and 1,800     pounds per cubic yard,
这取决于牛的饮食中有多少纤维。
depending on how much, uh,    fiber's in the cows' diet.
我觉得这个有很多。
I think this one had a lot.
好了，我们拿些铲子进来。
Alright, let's get      some shovels in here.
-是的，是的，铲子。谢谢你！-是的，是的，是的。
-Yes, Yes, shovels. Thank you.  -Yes, yes, yes.
这要花多长时间?
MITCH:  H-How long is this gonna take?
哦，不久。一两个小时。
Oh, not long.          Hour or two.
不，我还得再呼吸一个小时。
No, I cannot breathe in this   for another hour.
欧文:嗯，我想我们可以适合你
OWEN:         Well, I suppose         we could fit you
带着全脸防微粒呼吸器。
with a full-face       particle respirator.
莱拉:是的。气体的面具。
-LILA: Yes.           -Gas mask.
是的。是的，那个，谢谢。
Yes. Yes, that, please.
但如果我们要按规矩来，
But if we're gonna        go by the book,
这些都是出于医疗原因才使用的。
those are only deployed      for medical reasons.
上尉，你能看出什么医疗原因吗?
Captain, can you see       any medical reasons?
嗯…不，一个都没有。毫米。
Uh... no, not a one. Mm.
这样的话，就由我来决定了
Well, in that case, it falls to the sole discretion
负责设备的消防员。
of the firefighter     in charge of equipment.
(嘲笑)那是谁?
(scoffs) And who's that?
(Lila低声呻吟)
(Lila whimpers)
-哦。(呻吟)哦，不。
-Oh. (groans)          -Oh, no.
欧文:怎么样，Marwani?
OWEN:    What do you say, Marwani?
-我们应该让他们休息一下吗?(呼出)
-Should we give 'em a break?   -(exhales)
这要看情况。
Now, that depends.
我们保证不管发生什么，我们都不会起诉。
We promise whatever happens,   we won't sue.
这很好。
That's good.
但我还需要一件事。
But I am gonna need       one more thing.
任何东西。救我们出去。
Anything. Just get us out.
嘿，伙计们，这里是Firefox
Hey, guys, Firefox here.
i run into some friends  in work today . /i> i> i run into some friends
I ran into some friends      at work today
和他们真的， 真的想说"嘿。"
and they really,      really wanna say "Hey."
——(漫不经心地):嘿。 -MARJAN MARWANI: Aw.
-(unenthusiastically): Hey.   -MARJAN MARWANI: Aw.
MATEO: 让我们帮你听 好一点
MATEO:      Let us help you to hear       a little bit better.
哦，看那个。 继续，伙计们。 -MATEO:开始
-MARJAN: Oh, look at that.     Go ahead, guys.   -MATEO: Here we go.
我是Lila Geralds. .
I'm Lila Geralds.
And i 'm Mitch. .
And I'm Mitch.
我们想要 表示衷心的感谢
And we'd like   to give our heartfelt thanks
勇敢的英雄奥斯汀消防队的。
to the brave heroes  of the Austin Fire Department.
勇敢地救了我们。  -Hey-oh!
-MITCH:     For bravely rescuing us.      -Hey-oh!
哦，是的。 救你于
Oh, yeah.       Rescuing you from...
另一个……糟糕的情况 是我们自己造成的
Another... crappy situation     of our own making.
好吧，代表126位， 我们想说 不客气
Well, on behalf of the 126,     we'd like to say     you're welcome.
哦，还有 你们中任何一个，呃，
Oh, and to         any of you who, uh,
在杰拉尔德的GoFundMe页面上捐款，
contributed         to the Geralds'         GoFundMe page,
我想让你知道 那10万的那个
I'd like you to know      that 100 grand of that
花在这辆车上 在那边的粪堆里
was spent on this car   in that dung pile over there.
是的。
Yeah.
所以我代表我的追随者…
So on behalf of my followers...
(笑)
(laughs)
…下次，为什么不 你们自己去筹资?
...next time, why don't      y'all go fund yourselves?
马特奥:哦!
MATEO: Oh!
好吧，那我们就继续谈新英格兰吧。
Alright, well, then,  let's stick with New England.
嗯…罗德岛怎么样?
Um... how about Rhode Island?
——:天意。 -TOMMY VEGA:是的。
-BOTH: Providence.         -TOMMY VEGA: Yes.
是啊，你有点在我面前炫耀了。
Yeah, you're showing off     a little bit for me.
好吧，那就给我纽约。
Alright, well, then         give me New York.
容易。这是纽约
Easy. It's New York.
(模仿蜂鸣器的嗡嗡声)不。
(imitates buzzer buzzing)    No.
不，这是个陷阱问题。
No, that's a trick question.
我知道感觉就像在纽约
I know it feels like New York
应该是纽约的首府
should be     the capital of New York,
但事实并非如此。
but it is not.
(叹气)什么时候我们 需要
(sighs) When are we        ever going to need
知道州首府?
to know state capitals?
一直都是。
All the time.
什么时候?
IZZY: Like when?
比如游戏节目。
Like for game shows.
笑吧。
-(laughs)          -TOMMY: Laugh.
当你错过的时候
When you miss out
一套全新的洗衣机和烘干机，
on a brand-new set      of washer and dryers,
就因为你不知道纽约的首府在哪里…
well, just because you didn't know the capital of New York...
奥尔巴尼。
Albany.
你在耍我吗?
Were you messin' with me?
你这是在耍妈妈吗?
Were you playing a trick     on mom right now?
别担心， 我们能行，好吗?
IZZY:         Don't worry,        we got this, okay?
IZZY和EVIE:我们得走了
IZZY AND EVIE:           We gotta go.
我对你的爱像月亮一样深。
I love you to the moon.
(吻)
(kisses)
-我去过奥尔巴尼，相信我，
-(Tommy chuckles)      -I've been to Albany,      and trust me,
首都真的应该是纽约。
the capital really        should be New York.
对吧?这就是我要说的。
Right?     This is what I'm saying.
他们真的需要解决这个问题。
They really need to fix that.
我喜欢现在女孩们捉弄你的样子。
I love how the girls        mess with you now.
(笑)这是最好的。只是…
(laughs)      It's the best. Just...
我不知道，看着他们变成真人。
I don't know, watching them    turn into actual people.
TK:是的。
TK: Yeah.
警监，我能问你个问题吗?
Cap, can I ask you a question?
确定。
Sure.
你一直都想为人父母吗?
Did you always        wanna be a parent?
从我第一个卷心菜娃娃开始。
Since my first       Cabbage Patch doll.
(咯咯地笑)太好了。
(chuckling) Love that.
所以这只是时间问题，而不是如果?
So it was a matter        of when not if?
不完全是。
Not exactly.
好像想要孩子是一回事，
It's like wanting to have kids  is one thing,
但是…能够拥有它们，
but... being able to have 'em,
那完全是另一回事。
that turned out to be    a whole other ball of wax.
不容易吗?
It wasn't easy?
我的生命之战。
Fight of my life.
真的吗?
Really?
我们认为这些都是理所当然的
Well, we take for granted    those things
我们认为这很容易，
that-that we think         will come easily,
然后当他们不这样做的时候
and-and then when they don't,
这是世界上最难的事情。
it's, it's the hardest thing   in the world.
你是怎么处理的?
How'd you handle it?
不是好。一开始是，呃…
Not well.  In the beginning it was, uh...
我是说，我很生气。
I mean, I was angry.
我又生气又沮丧，累死了。
I was angry and depressed    and bone-tired.
和…说实话，准备退出。
And... truth be told,      ready to quit.
为什么不呢?
Why didn't you?
查尔斯。
Charles.
是的。他让我相信所有这些心痛和挣扎
Yeah. He-he convinced me that all this heartache and struggle
这是值得的。
was gonna be worth it.
这样我就能重回拳台了
So I'd get back in the ring
然后从头再来一遍。
and start slugging it out    all over again.
他说得对吗?
Well, was he right?
这值得吗?
Was it worth the fight?
你怎么看?
What do you think?
来吧，来吧。伸展右腿。
JOE:      Come on, come on.      Extend that right leg.
好吧，来吧，Marj，现在你懂了。推动。推，推，推。
PAUL: Alright, come on,     Marj, now you got this.     Push. Push, push, push.
好吧?推，推，推。
All right? Push, push, push.
你能停下来吗?
Will you stop?
我在做理疗，又没生孩子。
I'm doing PT,      I'm not giving birth.
乔:呃，不过他说得对。
JOE:     Uh, he's right, though.
你的那条腿需要进一步伸展。
You need to get   more extension in that leg.
这是唯一能让你得到
That's the only way         you're gonna get
所有的力量都在你的臀屈肌。
all the strength        in your hip flexor.
保罗:嗯。我尝试。
-PAUL: Mm-hmm.           -I'm trying.
哦，得了吧。就像我兄弟尤达说的。
Oh, come on.   It's like my man Yoda says.
“没有尝试，只有行动。”
"Ain't no try, only do."
是啊，尤达从没中过枪。
Yeah, well, Yoda never       got shot in the gut.
我需要再延长20%的时间。
I need 20% more extension.
(呼气)
(exhaling)
好吧，对，对，对。是的，你说对了，Marj。
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.     Yeah, you got it, Marj.
你说对了!来吧!
You got it! Come on!
不错的工作。释放。
Nice job. Release.
-(叹气)-不错，消防员。
-(sighs)      -Not bad, firefighter.
(清嗓子)还不错吧?
(clears throat)         Not bad?
乔:嗯。
JOE: Mm-hmm.
我只是给了你完整的延期。
I just gave you full extension.
是的，你说了。我很庆幸我没有眨眼。
Yeah, you did.     I'm glad I didn't blink.
也许下次你可以拿得更久一点…两秒?
Maybe next time you can hold it for longer than... two seconds?
你真的是在吸取我的痛苦，对吧?
You really do just  feed off my misery, don't you?
我做的事。
I do.
而且很好吃。
And it is delicious.
(呵呵)
(both chuckling)
哦。我的1:15刚刚出现。
Ooh. My 1:15 just showed.
下周见。
See you next week.
再见。
See ya.
和平。
Peace.
怎么啦？
What?
你真的要装作什么都没发生过吗?
Oh, you really gonna act like  that didn't just happen?
我不知道你在说什么。
I don't know    what you're talking about.
我说的是你和教练乔
I'm talking about you      and trainer Joe
在那边跟人调情。
flirting it up       a storm over there.
(嘲笑)我们不是在调情。
(scoffs) We were not flirting.
嗯。好吧，不管那是什么，反正是开着的。
Hmm. Okay, well, whatever that was, it was on and poppin'.
-(手机铃声)-闭嘴。
-(cell phone chimes)       -Shut up.
(保罗笑)
(Paul chuckles)
(Marjan笑)
(Marjan laughs)
我的杰拉尔德的大便照片刚刚获得了100万个赞。
My Geralds' poopy picture    just hit a million likes.
最好的一周。
Best week ever.
是的，我想也是。
Yeah, I bet.
(铃声)
(chimes)
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
是什么?
What is it?
萨利姆和他的牙周病医生刚生了个孩子。
Salim and his periodontist    just had a baby.
♪
嗯。无意冒犯，一点都不可爱。
Eh. No offense,     it's not even that cute.
我是说，对于一个婴儿来说。
I mean, for a baby, I mean.
是的，它的头有点尖。
TK: Yeah,    its head is kinda pointy.
像个锥形头。
Like a Conehead.
谢谢,伙计们。你是最棒的。
Thanks, guys.         You're the best.
丑陋的婴儿。-是吗?
-Ugly baby.         -Is it, though?
你知道吗?把这个给我。
You know what?           Give me this.
-MARJAN:没有。-不。
-MARJAN: No.           -No.
首先，你不能再跟踪萨利姆了
First of all, you need     to stop following Salim
在社交上，马上。
on socials, like, immediately.
其次，你别再闷闷不乐了。
And second of all,     you need to stop moping.
我的灵魂被击中了。
I just got punched        in the soul.
别以为这是对灵魂的重击。
Well, don't think of it     as a punch in the soul.
就当是狠狠踢了你一脚。
Think of it      as a kick in the ass.
这有什么用呢?
And how's that    supposed to help exactly?
也许这就是宇宙的规律
Well, maybe this is        the universe's way
告诉你是时候回去了
of telling you that it's time  to get back out there
开始寻找真命天子
and start looking        for Mr. Right
而不是盯着自己的另一半。
instead of staring  in the rear-view at Mr. Wrong.
他说得对，Marj。-我不知道。
-TK:   He's got a good point, Marj.   -I don't know.
我还没准备好开始约会。
Look, I-I'm not ready      to start dating.
你和萨利姆两年前分手了。
You and Salim     broke up two years ago.
你的生命中应该有一些火花。
You deserve a few sparks     in your life.
我就是靠擦火花为生的。
I literally put sparks out    for a living.
你知道吗?即使我真的想开始约会，
You know what? Even if    I did wanna start dating,
这对我来说是一件大事。
it's a-a whole thing for me.
一件我从未做过的事。
A thing that I've actually    never done before.
那家伙必须是穆斯林。我希望有个监护人。
The guy has to be Muslim. I'd want there to be a chaperon.
——只是……-你是说像保姆那样?
-There's just...   -You mean like a babysitter?
我是说，这是规定吗?
I mean, is that like,      a rule or something?
因为我哥们阿米尔总是一个人跟姑娘约会。
'Cause my buddy Amir goes out  with chicks solo all the time.
不过他确实需要个保姆。
Though he could    actually use a babysitter.
(嘴巴)真的。那么我们在这里谈论什么呢?
-(mouths) True.       -TK: So what are we       talking about here,
像专业的监护人?
like a professional chaperon?
不，像我父亲，叔叔，表弟。
No, like my father,       uncle, cousin.
所以家庭。确实不错。
-So family.            -Exactly.
我的都在迈阿密。
And mine are all in Miami.
所以就算我准备好了，
So even if I was ready     to put myself out there,
我在这里没有家人。
I don't have any family here.
这是个不错的尝试，Marjan。
That's a nice try, Marjan.
你有一屋子的家人呢。
You got a houseful      of family right here.
当一个人是对的，他就是对的。
When the man's right,      he is right.
保罗:他说得对。
PAUL:         And he's right.
所以不要找借口，Marjan。
So no excuses, Marjan.
你想要个监护人，你有很多。
You want a chaperon,       you got plenty.
好啊!
Fine!
我会回到阿森特的
I'll get back on Ascent
更新我的个人资料。
and update my profile.
-走吧，Marj。南希:哇!
-Let's go, Marj.         -NANCY: Whoo!
让它开始吧!-这是个开始。
-PAUL: Gettin' it goin'!     -It's a start.
-好的吗?-你是说开始?
-Okay?     -What you mean a start?
一个约会软件是解决不了问题的。
Well, one dating app        ain't gonna cut it.
数到三。
You gotta be on three.
保罗:嗯。——至少。
-PAUL: Hmm.           -At least.
我是说，更多的泳池，更多的鱼。
I mean, you know,      more pools, more fish.
为什么我已经开始后悔了?
Why am I already         regretting this?
你会有起起伏伏。
You're gonna have ups   and you're gonna have downs.
永远不要太高，也不要太低。
Never get too high      and never get too low.
找到你的王子通常意味着要亲吻很多青蛙。
Finding your prince usually  means kissing a lot of frogs.
你必须一开始就接受
You have to accept        out of the gate
无论你做什么，
that no matter what you do,
其中一些日期将是畏缩的。
some of these dates       will be cringe.
太好了。
Great.
好吧，我们需要一个安全词。
Okay, we're gonna        need a safety word.
安全词?
A safety word?
哦,不。他说得对。
Oh, no. He is right.
外面太残酷了，Marjan。
It's brutal out there, Marjan.
所以监护人需要
So the chaperons          are gonna need
就像让我们知道的暗号
like a code word to let us know
什么时候给你拉开伞索。
when to pull       the ripcord for you.
♪♪
Assalamu alaikum. .
Assalamu alaikum.
Walaikum salam. .
Walaikum salam.
奥马尔，你喜欢喝茶吗?
So, Omar, uh, you like tea?
你是热的。-哇。(笑)
-You're hot.          -Wow. (laughs)
谢谢你！
Thank you.
不，我是说，你出了很多汗。
No, I mean, you're sweating quite profusely.
我的天啊。我很抱歉。
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
呃，你知道，我从来没有
Uh, you know, I've never--
我从来没做过这种事。
I've never done       one of these before.
我是说，就像约会一样。(尖呼出)
Like a date, I mean.       (sharp exhale)
我的意思是，我用我的fiancé。例——Ex-fiance。
I mean, I did with my fiancé.  Ex-- Ex-fiancé.
是的，我们12岁就认识了。
Yeah, we'd known each other   since we were 12.
他的名字叫萨利姆。他刚生了个孩子。
His name is Salim.        He just had a baby.
你吻了多少只青蛙，宝贝?
How many frogs did you      have to kiss, babe?
关键是，如果说迪士尼教会了我们什么，
The point is that if Disney   has taught us anything,
你要找的是那个王子
it's that the prince     that you're looking for
通常是你最想不到的人。
is usually the last guy     you'd expect.
这就是为什么你至少要插入一个安慰书呆子
That's why you gotta insert    at least one comfort nerd
加入阵容，Marj。
into the lineup, Marj.
-安慰书呆子?tk:是的。
-A comfort nerd?         -TK: Yeah.
你知道的，就是一个冷静的人，可以帮你减轻压力
You know, someone who's chill and will help take the ease off
到了约会的时候。
when it's time for,        you know, date day.
噢,是吗?那家伙长什么样?
Oh, yeah?  What does that guy look like?
这些是给你的。(笑)
These are for you. (chuckles)
哇!谢谢。
Wow! Thanks.
他们是美丽的。-哇。
-They're beautiful.       -Wow.
他们是美丽的。-它们是纸吗?
-They're gorgeous.         -Are they paper?
我真的很喜欢纸做的花。
I'm really into paper-based   floral arrangements.
比以氨为基础的肥料更可持续。(笑)
Way more sustainable than ammonia-based fertilizers. (chuckles)
环保，体贴。
Eco-friendly and thoughtful.
好吧，那个词是什么来着?
Okay, well, what's the word?
我一直很喜欢“芜菁甘蓝”这个词。
I've always liked       the word "rutabaga."
(咯咯地笑)要做到这一点有点棘手
(chuckles) It's gonna be   a little tricky to work that
来个谈话，队长。
into a conversation, Cap.
也许对你来说。
Maybe for you.
呃，好吧，那
MARJAN:      Uh, okay, how about--
“爆米花”怎么样?
how about, um, "popcorn"?
好吧，我想这也行。
Okay, I guess that works, too.
好吧。
Okay.
哈桑，如果你能描述一下
Hassan, if you were to describe
用一个词概括你的职业，是什么?
your occupation in one word,   what would it be?
企业家。——啊。
-Entrepreneur.          -Ah.
杰克·贝佐斯，你最好小心点，因为我要来了。
Jake Bezos, you better look out, 'cause I'm coming.
-走吧，宝贝!-耶!
-Let's go, baby!         -Yeah!
如果我告诉你有个健身房呢
What if I told you       that there was a gym
健身器械旁边的位置
where next to      every workout machine
有一个自拍站
there was a selfie station
也不需要穿衬衫。
and no shirts       were ever required.
生病的!哈桑:对吧?
-Sick!         -HASSAN: Right?
你得把这个概念藏起来，兄弟。
You gotta keep that concept   under your hat, bro.
我仍然在寻求风险投资。
I'm still out to VCs.
就像我的 teta，
It's like my teta        used to say,
“花开花落，都太快了。”
"Flowers bloom,   but are all gone too soon."
除了这些。(笑)
Except these. (laughs)
你的 teta吗?
Your teta?
它的意思是奶奶。
It means grandma.
是的，我知道。我是黎巴嫩。
Yeah, I know. I'm Lebanese.
-不。好的，没问题。
-No way.        -MARJAN: Yes way.
(Zain和Marjan笑)什么?
-(Zain and Marjan laugh)     -ZAIN: What?
你的资料里说你是一名税务律师。
So, uh, it says in your profile you're a tax attorney.
-是吗?-我就是干这个的。
-Is that right?         -It's what I do.
但我不是这样的人。
But it's not who I am.
这不是我的激情所在。
It's, it's not my passion.
哦。那么，你的激情是什么?
Oh. Well, what is your passion?
我在国际狗狗救援空间工作。
I work in the International Dog Rescue Space.
哇。
Wow.
这有点傻，
It's kinda dorky,
但是，我非常喜欢
but, uh, I love pretty much
哈利·波特。
anything Harry Potter.
说实话，我对世间的激情都持怀疑态度。
I'm suspicious of all   earthly passions, honestly.
现在，我痴迷于我的三角。
Right now, I'm obsessed     with my delts.
我众包资金安排航班
I crowdsource financing     to arrange flights
让狗远离街道
for dogs to get off the streets
在世界各地的国家和爱的家庭。
in countries all over the world and into loving homes.
我们把狗从伊朗空运到加拿大，
Uh, we fly dogs       from Iran to Canada,
哥斯达黎加，美国。
Costa Rica, the US.
需求是无穷无尽的。
The needs are, are endless.
这是难以置信的。
That's incredible.
我知道这听起来很傻
I know it sounds silly,
但我把他们当成我的孩子
but I think of them as my kids.
哦，不，这听起来一点都不傻。
Oh, no, that doesn't sound silly at all.
说到这个，你对孩子有什么看法?
And speaking of,   how do you feel about kids?
比如，有多少?
Like, how many?
八。八?
-Eight.             -Eight?
是的。除非你想要更多。
Yeah. Unless you want more.
你已经不年轻了，
Well, you're no longer      a spring chicken,
我们得抓紧时间，但是，
we'd have to hurry, but, um,
你的身材很强壮，所以…
your build is strong, so...
你觉得他们有卖爆米花吗?
Do you think       they serve popcorn?
哦，看看这里的时间有点……
Oh, look at the time     in here is somethin'...
爆米花。很晚了。
-Popcorn.        -PAUL: It's late.
那么，你对我有什么感觉
So, uh, how would        you feel about me
有了孩子后还要工作?
working after having children?
没关系。
Fine with it.
只要他们支持曼联。
As long as they root       for Man United.
从来没有!
Never!
阿森纳或者什么都没有。
Arsenal or nothing.
我很乐意做个家庭主父。
I'd be happy to be        a stay-at-home dad.
去吧，宝贝。
Do you, baby.
总得有人资助哈桑之梦。
Somebody's gotta fund      the Hassan Dream.
给人生目标加上标签。
Hashtag life goals.
我真的很想吃爆米花。
You know, I'd really        love some popcorn.
(嘲笑)在茶馆?
(scoffs)         In a tea house?
是的。
Yeah.
你为什么不去看看，宝贝?
Why don't you go check, baby?
呃,好吧。
Uh, okay.
这是多萝西。
This is Dorothy.
她在德黑兰的街道上失去了两只耳朵。
She lost her ears    on the streets of Tehran.
哦。
Aw.
她咬掉了玩具的耳朵
She chewed the ears off her toy
这样它们就匹配了。
so that they match.
这不是很神奇吗?
Isn't that amazing?
这是我见过的最美的东西。
Oh, that is the       most beautiful thing       I have ever seen.
在我为她找到一个永远的家之前，我不能休息。
I can't rest until    I find her a forever home.
是的。
Yeah.
你的房子是什么?
So what's your house?
我们有126个。
Oh, we work out of the 126.
tk:嗯。-不，我是说你的霍格沃茨房子。
-TK: Mm-hmm.       -No, I mean       your Hogwarts house.
就像我是拉文克劳。我打赌你也是。
Like I'm Ravenclaw.        I bet you are, too.
或斯莱特林。
Or Slytherin.
我的天啊。别告诉我你是赫奇帕奇的。
Oh, my God. Please don't   tell me you're a Hufflepuff.
我不是很喜欢哈利波特。
I'm not really into  the whole Harry Potter thing.
我不…
I don't...
你知道吗?我觉得这行不通。
You know what?       I don't think       this is gonna work.
嗯。
Huh.
嗯，那是一种经历。
Well, that was an experience.
我总是全力以赴。
I always go full throttle.
记得在Instagram上关注我。
Hey, make sure    to follow me on Instagram.
我一直在努力提升自己的形象。
I've been trying      to boost that profile.
非常感谢。
Would appreciate it.
发短信给我，兄弟。
Text me, bro.
我的男人。我喜欢那个傻乎乎的孩子。
My man.      I like the goofy kid.
嗯。
Hmm.
Marjan。队长链。
Marjan. Captain Strand.
-这是我的荣幸。同样。
-This has been such a pleasure. -Likewise.
但我该走了。
But I should        probably be going.
多萝西开始撕家具
Dorothy starts     tearing up the furniture
如果我晚饭时间迟到了
if I'm, uh,      late for dinner time.
所以，我们应该再做一次。
So, we should do this again.
我很乐意。
I'd love that.
再见。-MARJAN:再见。
-Bye.          -MARJAN: Bye.
(Marjan咯咯地笑)
(Marjan giggles)
-我想我们找到赢家了!——(欧文笑)
-I think we just found a winner! -(Owen chuckles)
我想我们找到了一个天使。
I think we just found an angel.
是的。(笑)
Yeah. (chuckles)
哦。(叹息)
Oh. (sighs)
哦，伙计，你看，任何人都可以
Oh, man, look,        literally anybody
可以被任命为牧师为你们主持婚礼。
can get ordained        to marry you guys.
-是吗?保罗:嗯。
-Yeah?          -PAUL: Mm-hmm.
TK:那意味着什么?
TK:     And what's that entail?
很简单，伙计。
PAUL:         It's easy, man.
我在网上做的。
I did it online.
怎么了，Marj?
What's up, Marj?
嘿，你有满格吗?
MARJAN: Hey, are you getting full bars?
因为我不认为我
'Cause I don't think I'm--
我觉得我没有得到完整的格数。
I don't think      I'm getting full bars.
-是的。是啊，我也是。
-Yeah.       -TK: Yeah, me, too.
-MARJAN:哦……-等等，保罗，你被任命了?
-MARJAN: Oh...  -Wait, Paul, you're ordained?
是的，我和我在芝加哥的表妹结婚了
PAUL:       Yeah, I married       my cousin in Chicago
-几年前。嗯。
-a couple of years back.     -Huh.
马特奥:怎么了?什么了?
MATEO:        What up? What up?
嘿，嘿。-怎么样，家人?
-PAUL: Hey, yo.      -How we doin', family?
有什么事吗?我们做得很好。
What's up? We doin' good.
除了Marj，她没有酒吧。
Except for Marj,         who has no bars.
事实上，我有酒吧，所以，是的。
Actually, I do       have bars, so, yeah.
姑娘，怎么了?
Girl, what is wrong?
是那个叫福扎的家伙。
It's that Fauza guy.
那是救狗的人吗
Is that the dog rescue guy
还是那个长得像奥马尔·谢里夫的年轻人?
or the young     Omar Sharif-looking guy?
-是同一个人。(南希笑)
-It's the same guy.         -(Nancy chuckles)
我们真的很合得来。
We really hit it off.
你知道吗，约会最后他说，
You know, the date literally ended with him saying,
"我们应该再来一次"现在什么都没了。
"We should do this again,"    and now nothing.
一个电话也没有，一条短信也没有。
Not a call or a single text.
南希:嗯。
NANCY: Hmm.
他的原话是什么?
What were his exact words?
再来一次还是改天再来一次?
Do this again    or do this again sometime?
我不知道。有区别吗?
I don't know.    Does it make a difference?
-当然。-这有很大不同，Marj。
-PAUL: Hell, yeah.     -Oh, it makes     a big difference, Marj.
那个“有时”限定词
That "sometime" qualifier
从具体到模糊。
takes it from the concrete    to the vague.
是的。细微差别很重要。
Yup. Nuance matters.
没人告诉我要记笔记。
Well, nobody told me    I should be taking notes.
你知道吗?我已经讨厌这样了。
You know what?       I hate this already.
-只说明你做对了。-(手机铃声)
-Just means      you're doing it right.      -(cell phone chiming)
马特奥(笑)
(Mateo laughs)
宝贝，谁在打你的电话?
NANCY: Baby, who is      blowing up your phone?
哦，是哈桑。
Oh, it's Hassan.
他邀请我去他的街头服饰快闪店
Uh, he invited me     to his streetwear pop-up
市中心。
downtown later.
哈桑吗?
Hassan?
等等，你要比我先去第二次约会吗?
Wait, so you're getting    a second date before I am?
(咯咯地笑)太好了。
(chuckles) That's great.
你知道吗?我要咬紧牙关
You know what?  I'm just gonna bite the bullet
我要给福扎发短信，看他是否感兴趣。
and I'm going to text Fauza   and see if he's interested.
-不，不，不!-你怎么了?
-No, no, no, no!     -What's wrong with you?
-不要，不要那样做。-为什么不呢?
-Don't-don't do that.      -Why not?
因为如果你先给他发短信，会显得你很渴。
Because if you text him first,  you're gonna look thirsty.
-嗯。-所以他可以先给我发短信，
-Mm-hmm.      -So it's okay for him      to text me first,
但反过来不是吗?
but not the other way around?
-是的。-为什么?
-Yes.              -Why?
(平静地)父权制。
(quietly) The patriarchy.
等一下，好吗?
Just wait it out      for a second, alright?
也许他只是想装酷什么的。
Maybe he's just trying  to play it cool or something.
为了什么?
For what?
这样他就能增加我的需求和焦虑
So that he can amp up     my neediness and anxiety
就为了用一条短信来缓解情绪吗?
only to relieve it in a rush with one single text?
你确定你以前没约过会?
You sure you've       never dated before?
你知道吗?
MARJAN:          You know what?
我才不会上你这鬼话的当。
I am not gonna fall   for this manipulative crap.
我正式把手机收起来了。
I'm officially      putting away my phone.
-好的吗?-(手机哨声)
-Okay?      -(cell phone whistles)
是，是他。
It, it's him.
他给我发短信。(咯咯地笑)
He text me. (giggles)
他给我发短信。
He text me.
(咯咯地笑)你真是个笨蛋。
(giggles) You're such a dork.
哦……
Oh...
她现在就在里面。
She is in it now.
是啊，她现在真的深陷其中了。
Oh, yeah,     she is really in it now.
(叹息)
(sighs)
亚西尔(通过语音信箱):我是亚西尔。 请留言
YASIR (over voice mail):      This is Yasir.      Leave a message.
(施工噪音)
(construction noise)
(车门丁当声)
(car door dinging)
(深呼气)
(deep exhale)
噢,亚希尔。
Oh, Yasir.
-(男人1吹口哨)-(男人2大叫)
-(man 1 whistles)         -(man 2 whoops)
-(继续吹口哨)-哇!
-(whistling continues)      -Whoo!
严重吗?猪!
Seriously? Pigs!
男:哦!
MAN: Oh!
(呼出)
(exhales)
嗨。
Hi.
检查?
Checking in?
不完全是。我丈夫已经入住了。
Not exactly.  My husband already checked in.
他叫亚西尔·卡里姆。
His name is Yasir Karim.
你能告诉我他在哪个房间吗?
Could you just tell me      which room he's in?
——K-A-R-I-M。对不起。
-It's K-A-R-I-M.        -DESK CLERK: Sorry.
我无权透露那个消息。
I'm not at liberty  to give out that information.
酒店政策。
Hotel policy.
我是他妻子，法拉·卡里姆。
I'm his wife, Fara Karim.
我有身份证，如果有帮助的话。
I have ID, if that helps.
事实上，它并没有。
It doesn't, actually.
我不能透露任何个人信息
I'm not allowed to give out    any personal information
关于我们的客人。
about our guests.
酒店政策。
Hotel policy.
我不是要他的社保号。
I'm not asking for   his Social Security number.
他的车在前面。我知道他在这里。
His car is out in front.     I know he's here.
那也许你该打给他
Well, then maybe you      should try calling him
问他住在哪个房间。
and asking him        what room he's in.
我一直在给他打电话。
I've been trying to call him.
接待员:天哪。
DESK CLERK: Jeez.
他不接电话。
He's not answering.
(声音沙哑)对不起。我很抱歉。
(voice breaking)      I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我…怀孕七个月了。
I'm... seven months pregnant.
好吧,嗯……
Okay, um...
好吧，我知道他和另一个女人在一起。
Okay, look, I know he's here   with another woman.
我只是想和他谈谈。
I just need to speak to him.
就像我在问你一样
You know,       like I'm asking you
作为一个人对另一个人。
as a human being     to another human being.
请。
Please.
再说一次，我必须这么做
And again, I'm gonna have to
提醒您一下我们酒店的政策。
remind you of our hotel policy.
我才不管你那愚蠢的酒店政策。
I don't care about    your stupid hotel policy.
去你的酒店政策。
The hell with you      and your hotel policy.
如果有必要，我会敲开这家酒店的每一扇门。
I will bang on every door   in this hotel if I have to.
接待员:女士。
DESK CLERK: Ma'am.
这真的不是酒店。
This really isn't a hotel.
这就是所谓的秘密汽车旅馆。
It's what you call         a no-tell motel.
所以我不会说出去。
So I'm not gonna tell.
相信我，你不是第一个妻子
Believe me,    you're not the first wife
谁来这里抓人
who's come in here        trying to catch
她出轨的丈夫。
her cheating husband.
-(喘息)-这周也没有，亲爱的。
-(gasps)   -Not even this week, honey.
好吧?
Okay?
现在我得请你离开了。
Now I'm gonna    have to ask you to leave.
你不能这样对待别人。
You cannot treat         people this way.
接待员:不客气
DESK CLERK:  Well, you're more than welcome
出去的时候填一张评论卡。
to fill out a comment card    on your way out.
评论卡片。
Comment card.
接待员:现在，在我叫警察之前你快走吧。
DESK CLERK:     Now, just go     before I call the cops.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
接待员:不客气。
DESK CLERK:         You're welcome.
(口 )            发表评论…
(mouths)            Comment...
(戏剧音乐播放)
(dramatic music playing)
(哽咽)
(whimpering)
(大幅咕哝声)
(grunts sharply)
(沉重的呼吸)
(heavy breathing)
♪♪
(吹口哨)
(whistling)
(声)
(rumbling)
♪♪
(Fara尖叫)
(Fara screaming)
(Fara咯咯地笑)
(Fara cackling)
这违反酒店规定吗?!
Is this against hotel policy?!
(咯咯地笑)
(cackling)
哇!
Whoo!
(哎呀,大叫)
(whoops, yells)
哇!
Whoo!
(普通员工)
(grunts)
(咯咯地笑)
(cackling)
(碎片隆隆)
(debris rumbling)
-(汽笛声)-(喇叭鸣)
-(siren wailing)          -(horn blares)
(模糊聊天)
(indistinct chatter)
这里到底发生了什么?
What the hell happened here?
显然，一个女人发生了激烈的争执
Apparently, a woman       had a heated dispute
和服务台职员一起。
with the desk clerk there.
然后就开始横冲直撞
Then went on a rampage
带着她从工地偷来的防滑方向盘。
with this skid steer she stole   from that construction site.
知道她为什么这么做吗?
Any idea what set her off?
据店员说，她已经怀孕七个月了
According to the clerk,   she's seven months pregnant
她丈夫和另一个女人在汽车旅馆里。
and her husband's somewhere in the motel with another woman.
-好吧，这样就行了。-是的。
-Well, that'll do it.      -Yeah.
知道她在哪吗?
Any idea where she is?
受害者，不是情妇。
The-the victim,        not the mistress.
是啊，被困在那堆东西下面。
Yeah, trapped      under that pile there.
汤米:她怀孕七个月了?
TOMMY: And she's      seven months pregnant?
知道她有没有受伤吗?
Do we know if she's injured?
她在说话，说她很好
She's talking, says she's fine,
但我们还没能联系到她确认。
but we haven't been able    to get to her to confirm.
好的，维加上尉，准备。
Alright, Captain Vega,      stand by.
我们得保护这片区域。
We gotta secure this area.
好了,126。
Alright, 126.
思特里克兰德，里卡多，夹板和支柱。
Strickland, Ricardo,       cribbing and struts.
加拉格尔，查维斯，马尔瓦尼，你们去撤离。
Gallagher, Chavez, Marwani,   you're on extraction.
-把我们的受害者/嫌疑人带出来。马特奥:没错。
-Get out our victim/suspect.   -MATEO: Yep.
让我们努力把这件事做完
Let's try to       get this thing done
在整个事件发生之前。
before the whole thing      comes down.
伙计们，大摇大摆，都准备好了。
Hey, guys, the strut,     it's all set over here.
MARJAN:好的。
MARJAN: Alright.
(团队聊天)
(team chattering)
我来推，你来撬三下。
MATEO:  I-I'll push, you pry on three.
好的，一，二，三。
Okay, one, two, three.
(普通员工)
(grunts)
马特奥:把这个拿开。
MATEO:    Get this out of your way.
(Marjan普通员工)
(Marjan grunts)
女士，你受伤了吗?
Hey, ma'am, are you hurt?
我不这么认为。
I don't think so, no.
你开门了吗?
You got the door?
好吧。孩子怎么样了?
Alright. How's the baby?
她在踢腿，但这并不新鲜。
She's kicking,       but that's not new.
好吧，抓住我的手，我们要
Okay, take my hand        and we're gonna
带你出去，好吗?
get you out of here, alright?
不，我要留在这里。你离开了我。
No, I'm gonna stay here.     You leave me.
这不是一个选择。整个笼子可能会坍塌
That's not an option.  This whole cage could collapse
-随时会毁了你和你的孩子(金属磨)
-and crush you  and your baby any second now.  -(metal grinding)
(叹气)一切都已经被粉碎了。
(sighs) Everything        is already crushed.
有什么不同?
What's the difference?
(声音嘶哑)我失去了一切。
(voice breaking)      I've lost everything.
这不是真的。你的孩子还在。
That's not true.    You still have your baby.
你们将拥有彼此。
You will have each other.
不，我不会。我要进监狱了。
No, I won't.     I'm gonna be in prison.
出轨的人会得到抚养权。
And the cheating cheater's    gonna get custody.
没有哪个法官会对一个孕妇严厉惩罚
No judge is gonna throw the book at a pregnant woman
她在为她的家庭而战。
who is fighting for her family.
-在德州也没有。-尤其是在德州。
-Not even in Texas.    -Especially not in Texas.
牵着我的手，让我们给你的宝贝女儿看看
So take my hand  and let us show your baby girl
她妈妈是多么坚强。
how strong her mom is.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
来，拿着这个。我明白了。
-MARJAN: Here, take this.    -MATEO: I got it.
法拉:好的。
FARA: Okay.
(普通员工)
(grunts)
你做得很好。来吧。
MARJAN:        You're doing great.             Come on.
法拉:(气喘吁吁)对不起。
FARA:       (panting) I'm sorry.
你是好的。来吧。
You're okay. Come on.
-她要出来了，上尉。-没错。
-She's coming out, Cap.      -PAUL: That's right.
♪
-(监控器哔哔声)-她的血压和生命体征正常。
-(monitor beeps)   -Her BP and vitals are good.
TK，胎儿监护仪怎么说?
TK, what's    the fetal monitor saying?
宝宝的心跳是199，队长。
Baby's heartbeat is at 199, Cap.
这很糟糕吗?
Is that bad?
有点快，
It is a little fast,
但这也是意料之中的
but that's also expected
考虑到你们俩经历的冒险。
given the adventure that   the two of you have been on.
西园医院会给你做检查的，
Uh, West Park will        take a look at you,
但我并不担心。
but I'm not concerned.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
谢谢你给我讲道理。
Thank you for    talking some sense to me.
-她怎么样?她很好。
-How's she doin'?        -TOMMY: She's good.
这位警官要和你谈谈。
This officer needs        to talk to you.
我被逮捕了，是吗?
Oh, I'm being arrested, huh?
恐怕是。
Afraid so.
你没必要给她戴上手铐吧?
You don't have     to handcuff her, do you?
我想我们可以跳过这部分，
I think we can skip that part,
但我必须宣读你的权利
but I do have to      read you your rights.
是的,很好。我明白了。
Yes, fine. I understand.
我聚氨酯——
I pu--
(模糊聊天)
(indistinct chatter)
亚西尔，你这个混蛋!
Yasir, you rat bastard!
(模糊的无线电杂音)
(indistinct radio chatter)
法拉?上帝会为此惩罚你的
-Fara?  -God's gonna get you for this
我妈妈也是!
and so is my mother!
-那是…-是
-Is that--            -Yeah.
是的，它是。
Yes, it is.
福扎，怎么回事，伙计?
Uh, Fauza, what the hell, dude?
Marjan吗?
Marjan?
等待。你认识她吗?你认识他吗?
Wait. You know her?       You know him?
不是亚西尔，不过是福扎。
Uh, not as Yasir,        but, yeah, Fauza.
法——那是他哥哥的名字。
FARA: Fa-- that's his brother's name.
他有一个双胞胎兄弟吗?
Does he have a twin?
法拉:呃，不。
FARA: Uh, no.
我的律师会告诉你的
Oh, you're gonna     hear it from my lawyers
还有我所有的叔叔们!
and all my uncles!
请带我走吧，先生。
Please take me away, sir.
不，你得跟他们一起去。
Um, no, you're       gonna go with them.
我…我们医院见。
I'll, I'll meet you         in the hospital.
好吧，让我们…
Well, let's, um...
你也可以忘了周六晚上的事。
You can forget about       Saturday night, too.
(叹气)这太令人失望了。
(sighs) This is        so disappointing.
你……
You...
都令人失望。
are a disappointment.
(警笛声响)
(siren chirps)
TK !真是个惊喜。
TK! What a nice surprise.
嘿，现在不方便吗?
Hey, is this a bad time?
不，不，不。一点也不
No, no, no. Not at all.
我知道我应该先打个电话，但是
I know I should        have called, but--
我闻到炸鸡味了吗?
Do I smell fried chicken?
也许吧。
Maybe.
爸爸，你太迷人了
TK:      Dad, are you crushing
一个人吃一整桶鸡肉?
an entire bucket     of chicken by yourself?
鸡桶。
Chicken buckets.
粗略的一天?
Rough day?
哦，是福扎。
Oh, it's Fauza.
-真让人失望。-是的。
-What a disappointment.     -Yeah.
它们掉下来的时候很奇怪
It's weird when they drop
你的前任配偶炸弹。
the preexisting       spouse bomb on you.
哦，对了。
Oh, that's right.
好吧，至少卡洛斯和他的离婚了。
Well, at least       Carlos divorced his.
无效，但是，是的。
Annulled, but, yes.
这对我们来说从来不是个问题。
And that was never        a question for us.
现在，孩子们的问题。
Now, the kids question.
哇，等一下。他有个孩子?
Whoa, wait a minute.       He has a kid?
-不，他没有孩子。-哦。(嘲笑)
-No, he-he doesn't have a kid.  -Oh. (scoffs)
我刚发现他从来都不想这么做。
I just found out     that he never wants to.
听起来你需要点鸡肉。
Sounds like you could      use some chicken.
(TK叹了口气)
(TK sighs)
-这怎么这么好?毫米。对吧?
-How's this so good?       -Mm. Right?
你知道我害怕什么吗，爸爸?
You know what scares me, Dad?
是关于我们的，
Is what it says about us,
我们从来没有讨论过。
that we've never        even discussed it.
我看你是故意回避谈话的。
It says to me you avoided   the conversation on purpose.
避免了吗?
Avoided?
我不回避。
I don't avoid.
我想你没问过TK孩子的事
I think you didn't         ask TK about kids
因为你知道他会怎么回答。
because you knew    what his answer would be.
我们在一个如此好的地方。
We're in such a good place.
而且，我们最近真的很忙。
Also, we've been        really busy lately.
三年了，卡利托斯?
For three years, Carlitos?
请帮忙
Por favor.
你得做得更好才行。
You're gonna   have to do better than that.
人们都很忙。这就是问题所在。
People get busy.        That's the thing.
是的，但是不太忙
Yeah, but not too busy
进行如此基础的对话。
to have a conversation      so foundational.
健康的夫妻不会这么做。
And that's not     what healthy couples do.
你妈妈和我从来没讨论过
You know, your mother      and I never discussed
你会信仰什么宗教
what religion you were gonna be
直到我无意中听到她在安排你的割礼
until I overheard her      scheduling your bris
在产房。
in the delivery room.
不用说，一场热烈的谈话随之而来。
Needless to say, a very  animated conversation ensued.
你不觉得是因为我上瘾了吗?
You don't think   it's because I'm an addict?
他担心我会旧病复发?
He's worried that I'll relapse?
也许这才是真正困扰你的。
Maybe that's what's      really bothering you.
不。我全心全意地相信TK的康复。
No. I believe in TK's recovery  with my whole heart.
这就是他说的原因吗?
Is that what he said       the reason was?
不。他说是因为他想让我们去环游世界。
No. He said it's because he wants us to travel the world.
(笑)
(laughs)
怎么啦？我这辈子只离开过这个州两次。
What?    I've only left the state,    like, twice in my life.
我们两次都得让你又踢又叫。
And we had to take you      kicking and screaming      both times.
(咯咯地笑)在布兰森过了一个周末后，你想家了。
(chuckles) You got homesick   after a weekend in Branson.
Ay, mi amor. .
Ay, mi amor.
你为什么不告诉我你到底在烦恼什么?
Why don't you tell me   what's really bothering you?
说实话，我觉得大声说出来不太舒服。
Honestly, I don't feel comfortable saying it out loud.
是你担心吗
Is it that you're worried
孩子的生命中没有母亲了吗?
that the child's not gonna   have a mother in their life?
因为我在你身边，你的姐妹们也是。
Because I'm here for you,    and so are your sisters.
我知道。
I know you are.
我不担心孩子的母亲会是谁。
I'm not worried about     who the mother will be.
我很担心谁会成为孩子的父亲。
I'm worried about  who's going to be the father.
我说的不是TK。
And I don't mean TK.
都怪你。加吗?
-TK: I blame you.        -Me?
是啊，因为我现在父子关系很好，
Yeah, because    I have such a great    father/son situation here,
我想把爱传递出去。
I wanted to, you know,      pay it forward.
TK和欧文一直有着特殊的关系
TK and Owen have always had   such a special relationship
从他很小的时候开始。
from the time he was little.
直到两年前我才开始和我爸爸一起做。
I didn't start one with my dad  until two years ago.
事实并非如此。
That is not true.
恐怕我达不到标准。
I'm afraid I won't measure up.
但我也不想逼他做什么
But I also don't wanna     push him into something
他不想要的。
that he doesn't want.
这让我有同情心还是自私?
Does that make me    compassionate or selfish?
我不能回答这个问题，但我可以告诉你
I can't answer that,     but what I can tell you
几乎每次我都把你妈妈的需求放在我的需求之前
is almost every time I put your mother's needs before mine,
结果我更快乐了
I ended up being happier
如果我得到了我想要的
than if I'd gotten     what I thought I wanted.
你是说我应该放弃这个梦吗?
So you're saying   I should give up the dream?
不。
No.
我的意思是你得体谅别人
What I'm saying is that    you have to be considerate
他的感受和你的感受一样重要。
for his feelings    just as much as your own.
不管你怎么决定…
And whatever you decide...
你得跟他说实话。
you have to be         honest with him.
接受宇宙给予你的一切。
And take what     the universe gives you.
因为无论发生什么， mijo，
Because no matter        what happens, mijo,
最重要的是……
the most important thing...
是TK在我身边。
Is that TK's by my side.
…因为卡洛斯是我的人。
...'cause Carlos is my person.
♪♪
好吧。我有葡萄叶，米饭，还有大蒜。
Okay. I got grape leaves,  I got rice, and I got garlic.
你得到薄荷。我去拿阿勒颇胡椒。
You get the mint.           I'm gonna get        the Aleppo pepper.
正确的。我们需要snoubar。
Right. And we need snoubar.
Snoubar吗?什么是snoubar?
Snoubar? What is snoubar?
可能在松子下面。
Probably under pine nuts.
不，阿莎对坚果过敏。
Oh, no,     Asha's allergic to nuts.
-哦。-如果我们不用它会毁了它吗?
-Oh.       -Is it gonna ruin it       if we don't use it?
不，一切都很好。
No, it's all good.
其实，我想说谢谢你。
Actually, you know,   I-I wanted to say thank you.
谢谢你们请我来吃晚饭。
Um, I appreciate you guys   inviting me over for dinner.
但是，如果你想一个人过夜
But, you know, if you wanna   spend the night alone
作为夫妻，我完全理解。
as a couple, I totally get it.
我不想当电灯泡。
I don't wanna be          a third wheel.
Marjan，我们不是在邀请你。你在帮我做饭。
Marjan, we are not inviting you. You're helping me cook.
不然我还能做什么
How else am       I supposed to make a
正宗的黎巴嫩薄饼?
authentic    Lebanese mezze by myself?
-(笑)是啊，那会是一场灾难。(嘲笑)
-(chuckles) Yeah,    that would be a disaster.    -(scoffs)
-好的，我们需要茄子做印度辣酱。-是的。
-Okay, we need eggplant     for baba ghanoush.     -Yes.
两个:哦!
BOTH: Oh!
保罗:哦。教练乔。-嘿，你们两个!
-PAUL: Oh. Trainer Joe.     -Hey, you two!
嘿。
Hey.
你，你在这里做什么…
What are you,    what are you doing here...
在清真市场?
in a halal market?
我只吃清真肉
Well, I only eat halal meat,
我觉得自己就像上等腰牛排
and I felt like a porterhouse.
你是穆斯林?
You're Muslim?
这真的令人震惊吗?
Is that really such a shock?
是的，有点，你知道的。
Yeah, kinda, you know.
因为我是布莱克，我叫乔?
Because I'm Black        and my name is Joe?
我逗你是因为我是黑人
I was only messing with you   because I am Black
但我其实叫优素福。
but my name is actually Yusuf.
(笑)。
(laughs) Right.
好吧，那你怎么从来没提过
Okay, well, how come you     never mentioned that
在我们的疗程中?
in any of our sessions?
我为什么要这么做?我不会把个人生活带到工作中。
Why would I? I don't bring     my personal life to work.
-是的，我尊重这一点。是的。乔:是啊。
-Yeah, I respect that. Yeah.   -JOE: Yeah.
Assalamu alaikum. .
Assalamu alaikum.
Walaikum salam. .
Walaikum salam.
(笑声)
(laughter)
好吧。很高兴能遇到你，乔。优素福。
Alright. It was, uh, it was nice running into you, Joe. Yusuf.
你也是。周四见。
Uh, you, too.      I'll see you Thursday.
实际上,嗯…
Actually, uh...
也许你今晚想见我?
maybe you wanna see me tonight?
我要去这家伙家
I'm-I'm going       to this guy's house
和女朋友一起吃晚饭
with his girlfriend for dinner,
我真的需要一个电灯泡
and I could really use      a fourth wheel.
我不知道。
I don't know.
我的天啊。我很抱歉。
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉。当我没问。
I'm sorry.       Forget I even asked.
乔:我想说，我不知道
JOE:         I was gonna say,         I don't know
如果一份上等腰牛排就够了。
if one porterhouse         would be enough.
你在耍我。乔:啊。
-You're messin' with me.     -JOE: Aah.
-我逗你玩呢。-(Marjan, Joe笑)
-I was messing with you.     -(Marjan, Joe laugh)
我很乐意。
I would love to.
-是吗?乔:是啊。
-Yeah?           -JOE: Yeah.
酷。(笑)
Cool. (laughs)
-他想让我——是的。-是的。是的，他喜欢。
-He wants me to-- Yeah.     -Yes. Yes, he does.
(街道环境噪音)
(ambient street noise)
-嘿,宝贝。-你好。完美的时机。
-Hey, babe.       -Hi. Perfect timing.
你今天过得怎么样?改善情况。
-How was your day?        -Good.
-你在做饭?威灵顿牛肉。
-What are you cooking?      -Beef Wellington.
要我给你拿杯酒吗?
Can I get you a glass of wine?
首先，告诉我是什么场合。
First, tell me the occasion.
任何场合。
No occasion.
只是和你在一起的每一晚
Just every night that     I get to spend with you
是一个值得庆祝的夜晚。
is a night worth celebrating.
别担心。
Don't worry.
这不是贿赂。
This isn't a bribe.
这个也不是。
Well, neither is this.
(咯咯地笑)这是什么?
(chuckles) What is this?
这是个惊喜。
It's a surprise.
(模仿布拉德·皮特)盒子里是什么?
(imitating Brad Pitt)       What's in the box?
盒子里是什么?
What's in the box?
你演得像极了布拉德·皮特，知道吗?
You do a horrible Brad Pitt,   you know that?
我知道，但你喜欢。
I know, but you love it.
其实我不喜欢，但我爱你。
I don't, actually,        but I do love you.
-那么，去吧，打开它。——(TK吸入)
-So, go on, open it.       -(TK inhales)
(TK呼出)
(TK exhales)
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
有胡子的龙?
A bearded dragon?
-宝贝，这太可怕了
-Babe, it's--          -Terrifying.
美丽。
Beautiful.
哇。
Wow.
嘿，小家伙。
Hey, little buddy.
嘿。(笑)
Hey. (chuckles)
嘿，小家伙。
Hey, little guy.
我知道你准备好当父亲了。
I know you're ready       to be a father.
我毫不怀疑你会成为一个了不起的人。
And I have no doubt that   you would be an amazing one.
但我不确定我能做到。
But I'm not so sure       I'm there yet.
或者永远不会。
Or ever will be.
TK:嗯。
TK: Hmm.
我只是想跟你说实话
I just wanted      to be honest with you
说这可能是唯一的孩子
and say that    this may be the only child
我们曾经一起分享过。
we ever share together.
好吧。
Okay.
好吧?
Okay?
好吧。
Okay.
真的吗?你确定吗?
Really? Are you sure?
卡洛斯，你能接受我的同意吗?
Carlos, would you        just take the yes?
好吧。
Okay.
是的,TK。
Yes, TK.
而且，他们告诉我它喜欢吃活蟋蟀。
Also, they told me  it likes to eat live crickets.
-那就是你的工作了。——(TK笑)
-So, that's gonna be your job.  -(TK laughs)
我明白了。
TK:            I got it.
我们该给这个小家伙取什么名字?
What should     we name this little guy?
我在想路易二世或者卢二世。
I was thinking Louis the Second or Lou II.
我们为什么不问问他呢?让我们看看他更喜欢哪一个。
Why don't we ask him?      Let's see which one      he likes better.
-好的。-好的。
-Okay.              -Okay.
哦,废话。
Ohh, crap.
他已经出来了，不是吗?
He already got out,       didn't he?
不可能走远，对吧?
Couldn't have         gone far, right?
路易二世?
Uh, Louis the Second?
(咕哝)路二世?
(grunts) Lou II?
我再也睡不着了。
I'm never sleeping again.
哦,男孩。
Oh, boy.
Point.360的标题
Captioned by Point.360